(Leonard:)Also, we both think
I'm not funny.
(quiet, nervous laugh)
(Leonard:)Huh? See, you're not laughing.
(Skype ringing)
(Mike(on Skype):)Hey, Froot Loops, what's up?
(Howard:)Hey, Mike.
(Howard:)Listen, NASA asked me to
(Howard:)throw out the first pitch
at an Angels game.
(Howard:)You got any advice?
(Mike:)Yeah. Don't do it.
(Mike:)What else you up to?
(Howard:)Why shouldn't I do it?
(Mike:)There's no upside.
(Mike:)If you do well, no one cares.
(Mike:)And if you screw up,
(Mike:)you're an idiot
on YouTube forever.
(Howard:)But it's for a good cause.
(Howard:)What about all the kids
that'll be there?
(Mike:)That's what I'm telling you.
(Mike:)Kids are the worst.
(Mike:)My own daughter tweeted
I have a giant nose.
(Howard:)Well, maybe I'll do a good job.
(Mike:)I don't know.